

Marko Gobeljic

Full Stack Developer

Information

Address:

Dr Ivana Ribara 015, Novi Sad 21000, Serbia

Email:

gobeljic.mmarko@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/marko-gobeljic

Profile Summary

Full Stack Web and Mobile enthusiast with more than 8 years of experience in JavaScript, PHP, Python programming and Cryptocurrency technologies.

I mastered Computer Software Engineering and hold Bachelor's degree in Computer Science.

As a JavaScript geek, I love JavaScript and worked a lot with JavaScript based frameworks and libraries. Especially I have got rich experience with JavaScript based SPA such as React, Vue and Angular recently.

I have also worked with other languages such as PHP (mostly Laravel), Python(mostly Django) and e-commerce platforms such as Shopify and WooCommerce.

My core competency lies in complete end-end management of a new website development project, and I am seeking opportunities to build websites and mobile apps from the ground up for you or your business.

Work Experience

Jun 2019 - Oct 2020

Senior Full Stack Developer

ACTANO GmbH, Germany

- Developed parking management dashboard using React/Redux - Used Material UI to implement the design
- Implemented authentication using Keycloak
- Used ApexCharts library to show the parking status
- Implemented video stream to show real time status in parking area

Sep 2018 - May 2019

Senior React, Node Developer

ACTANO GmbH, Germany

- Developed Redux, Redux-Saga, Redux thunk
- Rich and well-structured analysis platform.
- Worked with JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Al, d3.js, Algorithms, Al, ML.
- Automated testing suites, like Jest
- DevOps such as CI/CD, Jenkins

Skill Sets

- JavaScript, React, Vue, Angular, Typescript, Purescript
- Node, Express, Sails, Meteor
- PHP, Laravel
- Python, Django
- Shopify, WordPress, WooCommerce
- React Native, Flutter
- Various JS libraries related canvas and chart such as HighCharts.js,
- AmCharts.js, Fabric.js, Three.js, Pixi.js and etc.
- Blockchain

Apr 2017 - Sep 2018 Web and Mobile Developer

Mycointainer, Estonia

- Use back office UI/UX from custom graphic design to React/Typescript based components.
- Used the React-Redux, Redux-Saga based on MVC Architecture patterns and TDD
- Keep the quality with automated testing (Jest)
- Building CI/CD Pipeline using Jenkins and dockers
- Simplified and Accelerated the project workflow by using the Docker
- Focused on-page optimization, performance, SEO-friendly approaches.
- Converted the business requirements into optimum DB schema and writing performing queries.
- Awesome animations and transitions using CSS/SCSS

Aug 2016 - Aug 2018 Front-End Developer

Mycointainer, Estonia

- Used semantic component framework Vuetify.js which supports server-side rendering, single-page apps, progressive web apps, and standard HTML pages.
- Using the Tailwin CSS because it is much faster and easier to build and refactor UI
- Managing the Migration, Seeding, Eloquent model, Routing, Authentication, Middleware, ORM, Unit testing, Artisan in Laravel
- Used the Laravel packages like Spark, Cashier, Vapor, Horizon, and many others.

Jan 2016 - Aug 2016 Senior Software Engineer

HotLap

- Implemented a RESTful Node.js server as the lead back-end developer.
- Deployed to AWS and maintained the servers with basic Linux administration.
- Built a mock-up of the front-end web app using React/Redux, wiring up all the API calls to the back-end.

May 2014 - Jan 2016 Senior Software Engineer

HotLap

- Worked with marketing teams to establish Facebook ads and Google AdWords strategies.
- Leveraged pixel-conversions to optimize targeting and increase revenue per click.
 Designed a MongoDB database.
- Created single-page apps with Backbone.js and Ember.js.
- Developed software using RESTful APIs with Node.js and Express.js.
- Handled JavaScript UX framework prototyping.
- Created reusable D3.js charts using Raphael.js to draw SVG on browsers.

Feb 2012 -Mar 2014 Front-End Developer

Netfork

- Worked on enterprise-level Supply Chain and Logistic web application using Angular and TypeScript
- This project is currently used by McKesson, AWS, and other partners
- Used Agile Software development methodology and scrum methodology for project development
- Collaborated with team members through Slack and Azure DevOps
- Implemented complicated Stories and Epics
- POs, Pallets, Doors, DoorGroups, Docks, Thresholds, Reservations, Cloures, Vendors, Carriers, and so on.

Education

2008 - 2011 University of Novi Sad

Bachelor's Degree

Faculty of Technical Sciences